<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homes on Pouya Samangouei</title>
    <link>https://po0ya.github.io/home/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homes on Pouya Samangouei</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://po0ya.github.io/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://po0ya.github.io/home/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://po0ya.github.io/home/about/</guid>
      <description>Biography Got my Ph.D. at the University of Maryland, College Park, under supervision of Rama Chellappa. I worked on various computer vision and machine learning problems while doing my Ph.D.: attribute detection for mobile phones, face detection, compressed sensing with GANs, defending deep networks using GANs, and explaining black-box classifiers with GANs. Now a machine learning scientist at Butterfly Network working with Nathan Silberman to make medical imaging intelligent, cheap, and accessible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News</title>
      <link>https://po0ya.github.io/home/news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://po0ya.github.io/home/news/</guid>
      <description>Jul18: Officially Dr. Pouya Samangouei. Jul18: Explain-GAN is accepted in ECCV18 (link). Apr18: Defense-GAN code is released. Mar18: Face-Magnet code is released. Mar18: Face-MagNet paper is published in WACV18 and is on arxiv. Feb18: CSGAN code is released. Jan18: Happy to see the ICLR18 oral paper AmbientGAN is very related to Algorithm 2 of our AAAI18 paper. Jan18: DefenseGAN is accepted in ICLR18. Jan18: Started my spring research internship at Butterfly Network with Nathan Silberman.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://po0ya.github.io/home/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://po0ya.github.io/home/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>